The magic didn't end at midnight.
Cinderella II: Dreams Come True is a family, animation,
romance film directed by John Kafka.
As a newly crowned princess, Cinderella quickly learns that life at the Palace - and
her royal responsibilities - are more challenging than she had imagined.
In three heartwarming tales, Cinderella calls on her animal friends and her Fairy Godmother to help as she brings her own grace and
charm to her regal role and discovers that being true to yourself is the best way to make your dreams come true.
Cinderella (voice), played by Jennifer Hale.
Jaq / The Baker / Sir Hugh / Grand Duke / Bert / Flower
Vendor (voice), played by Rob Paulsen.
Gus / Mert / Stable Hand (voice), played by Corey Burton.
The King (voice), played by Andre Stojka.
Fairy Godmother / Mary Mouse / Beatrice / Daphne / Drizella /
Countess Le Grande (voice), played by Russi Taylor.
Lady Tremaine (voice), played by Susanne Blakeslee.
Cinderella II: Dreams Come True (also known as Cinderella 2: Dreams Come True) is a 2002 American animated
direct-to-video fantasy anthology film and serves as the sequel to the 1950 film Cinderella.
Directed by John Kafka from a screenplay written by Jill E.
Blotevogel, Tom Rogers, and Julie Selbo, it is the first in the Cinderella franchise to use digital ink and
paint and stars the voices of Jennifer Hale, Russi Taylor, Corey Burton, and Rob Paulsen.
The film centers on Jaq, Gus, the Fairy Godmother, and the rest of the mice, as they create a three-story narrative about what happened after
Cinderella married Prince Charming and moved in his castle along with the mice, her stepsisters, and Lady Tremaine's cat, Lucifer.
Cinderella II: Dreams Come True was released on February 26, 2002, and received
generally negative reviews from critics, though it recouped its budget.
The film explores themes of princess, magic, fairy, cartoon, musical.
The tone is uplifting and emotional.